♪The sun rests on the sea♪
♪ الشمس تسقط في البحر ♪
♪The sky steals the night and day♪
♪ تسرق السماء الليل والنهار ♪
♪The waves tug at my heartstrings♪
♪ سدّ الأمواج عند نبضات قلبي ♪
♪That's the petals' curtain call♪
♪ هذا هو مكالمة فائتة للبثلاث ♪
♪The wind is blowing on my face♪
♪ الرياح تهمر على وجهي ♪
♪I'm stroking the fragile film♪
♪ أنا أشاهد الفيلم الهش ♪
♪Memories spread under the streetlamps♪
♪ ذاكرة تنتشر تحت مصابيح الشوارع ♪
♪The stars linger in the Milky Way♪
♪ النجوم مبطنة في طريق الميلكي ♪
♪I've sung every song♪
♪ لقد أغنت كل أغنية ♪
♪You remember it all♪
♪ أنت تتذكر كل شيء ♪
♪I cried, you laughed♪
♪ بكيت، ضحكت ♪
♪You said you would be with me♪
♪ قلت إنك ستكون معي ♪
=Six Sisters=
= ست راهبات =
=Episode 18=
= الحلقة 18 =
Who is it?
من هي؟
Fang Tao. It's Lina.
فانغ تاو، إنها لينا
What's up?
ما الأمر؟
Open the door.
افتح الباب
Let me in and we'll talk.
دعني أدخل وسنتحدث
Fang Tao.
فانغ تاو
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
Let me in.
سأدخل
Say it here.
قلها هنا
What else could it be?
ماذا يمكن أن يكون غير ذلك؟
It's about us.
الأمر يتعلق بنا
What could it be between us?
كيف يمكن أن يكون بيننا؟
Fine, if you think it's ok,
حسنًا، إن كنت تظن أنه أوك
I'll say it here.
أقول ذلك هنا
- Come in. - That's more like it.
- تعال - هذا أحسن
Anything to eat?
أي شيء للأكل؟
I'm hungry after a long walk.
أنا جائعة بعد مسيرة طويلة
Who is it?
من هو؟
Me.
أنا
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني؟
You want me to go to your room
تريدني أن أذهب إلى غرفتك
and throw myself at you?
بإلقاء نظرة عليك؟
In your dreams!
في أحلامك!
Jiahuan, I didn't mean that.
جياهوان، لم أقصد ذلك
My workplace is allocating housing
مكان العمل الخاص بي يخصص السكن
and I've applied for a unit.
وقد تقدمت بطلب للحصول على وحدة
It's a bit small,
إنها صغيرة بعض الشيء
but it's furnished.
لكنه مؤثث
If you're annoyed with me,
إذا كنت منزعجا مني
you can move in there.
يمكنك الدخول إلى هناك
Who wants to live there?
من يريد أن يعيش هناك؟
What Ouyang Bao said is not true.
ما قاله أويانغ باو ليس صحيحًا
We have a misunderstanding.
لدينا سوء تفاهم
Then let's adopt to it.
إذن دعنا نتبنى ذلك
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Aren't you afraid that people will know?
ألا تخشى أن يعرف الناس؟
I don't care!
لا يهمني!
Jiahuan,
جياهووان
I've been thinking about it for a long time.
أنا أفكر في الأمر منذ وقت طويل
I think the main problem
أظن أن المشكلة الرئيسية
is that we're too different.
هي أننا مختلفون جدًا
I don't think I deserve you.
لا أظن أنني أستحق ذلك
It's not your call.
هذه ليست اتصالك
It's my call!
هذه اتصالي!
Fang Tao, can you be a little confident?
فانغ تاو، هل يمكنك أن تكوني واثقة بعض الشيء؟
You're not that bad!
أنت لست بذلك السوء!
I don't think you don't deserve me.
لا أظن أنك لا تستحقين مني
But you must tell me
لكن يجب أن تخبريني
why your ex-wife came to you again.
لماذا أتت زوجتك السابقة إليك مجددًا
- She... - Is she here to make up with you?
- إنها... - هل هي هنا للتعويض معك؟
So you were like
إذًا كنت مثل
a dry faggot on a blazing fire.
اشتعلت النار في شجار جاف
When you were in the room,
عندما كنت في الغرفة
was your love rekindled?
هل أعيد إذكاء حبك؟
No!
لا
She just covets my house.
إنها تطمع منزلي فحسب
I made it clear to her.
أوضحت لها ذلك
I told her it was never going to happen!
قلت لها ألا يحدث ذلك أبدًا!
Jiahuan,
جياهووان
if you really accept me,
إذا كنت تقبلني حقا
I'll cook for you for the rest of my life.
سأطبخ لك لبقية حياتي
I'm willing to take care of you.
أنا على استعداد لأعتن بك
Look what I just ate.
انظري ما أكلته للتو
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا
I'll never let you eat pickles again.
لن أسمح لك بتناول المخللات مجددًا أبدًا
It's all your fault.
كل هذا بسببك
Fang, I'm sorry about last time.
فانغ، أنا آسفة بشأن المرة الماضية
I had a few drinks
كنت أتناول بعض المشروبات
and said something wrong.
وقال شيئًا خاطئًا
You've got a great personality.
لديك شخصية رائعة
Let's look out for each other.
لنساعد بعضنا البعض
We can spend more time together.
يمكننا قضاء المزيد من الوقت معًا
- Ok. - Come.
- حسنا - هيا
Bro.
شكرا لك
Welcome to join us.
أهلا للانضمام إلينا
Here comes the fish.
ها قد أتت السمك
- Here. - The food is all ready.
- تفضلي - الطعام جاهز تمامًا
Let's eat, Xiaoling. Time to eat.
لنأكل يا شياو دينغ حان وقت تناول الطعام
Let's eat.
لنأكل
Won't you drink up?
ألن تشربي؟
I will.
سأفعل
It's the Lantern Festival today.
إنه مهرجان الفوانيس اليوم
Let's welcome Fang Tao to join us.
دعنا نرحب بالسيد فانغ تاو للانضمام إلينا
- Come. - From now on, you're family.
- هيا - من الآن فصاعدًا، أنت عائلة
- Thanks, Jiali, everyone. - Welcome.
- شكرًا يا جيالي جميعًا - مرحبًا
Where is Jianguo?
أين جينجو؟
He's working overtime.
إنه يعمل وقتا إضافيا
Welcome.
أهلًا بك
Fang,
فانغ
you really did a good thing.
لقد فعلت حقا شيئا جيدا
Jiahuan
جياهووان
is a bully in the family.
هو متنمر في الأسرة
Once you marry her and tame her,
بمجرد الزواج منها وترسيمها
the world will be at peace.
سيكون العالم في سلام
Ouyang, what are you talking about?
أويانغ عمّ تتحدث؟
You're talking nonsense after a few drinks.
تتحدثين هراء بعد بعض المشروبات
No, no. I've just started drinking.
لا، بدأت أشرب للتو
Fang Tao, I'll drink to you.
فانغ تاو، سأشرب لك
- I'll join you. - Zhenmin.
- سأنضمّ إليكم - زنمين
Only Jiawen is absent.
جيوين فقط متغيب
Why didn't she come?
لماذا لم تأتي؟
Well, Weiguo
حسنًا يا فييغو
and Guangming didn't come either.
وغوانغ مينغ لم يأت أيضًا
Weiguo is also working overtime.
ويغو يعمل أيضًا لوقت إضافي
Jiawen went to her mother-in-law's.
ذهبت جيان وين إلى حماتها
Yeah.
نعم
Though she didn't come, her care arrived.
رغم أنها لم تأت انتبها إلى الوصول
She sent a monetary gift, right?
أرسلت هدية نقدية، صحيح؟
Fang Tao,
فانغ تاو
it's the holiday. Make a toast.
إنه العطلة، اصنع نخب
Grandma, Mom,
جددا يا أمي
thanks for raising a great daughter.
شكرًا على تربية ابنة عظيمة
I'd like to recite a poem
أود أن أتلاعب بقصيدة
to express my feelings right now.
للتعبير عن مشاعري الآن
A poem, wow.
قصيدة يا إلهي
Her smile is like a flower
ابتسامتها مثل زهرة
lighting up the road ahead of me.
إضاءة الطريق أمامي
I will cherish her forever
سأعتز بها إلى الأبد
with all my passion and persistence.
بكل حمايتي ومثابرتي
Great!
رائع!
Good.
جيد
Good poem.
قصيدة جيدة
- What a poet. - Come on!
- يا له من شاعر - يا له من شاعر - هيا!
Happy Lantern Festival!
مهرجان الفوانيس سعيد!
Welcome!
أهلًا بكم!
So talented.
موهوب جدًا
You're good.
أنت صالحة
You must have read a lot.
لا بد أنك قرأت كثيرًا
I didn't write it.
لم أكتب ذلك
Fang Tao, please
فانغ تاو، من فضلك
take care of Jiahuan from now on.
اعتني بجياهان من الآن فصاعدًا
- Rest assured, Mom. - Mom.
- اطمئني يا أمي - أمي
I'll have to take care of him.
يجب أن أعتني به
You take care of each other.
عليكما أن تهتم ببعضكما البعض
Who cooks filefish for whom?
من يطهو المصفاة لمن؟
Jiali!
جيالي!
By the way, Fang Tao,
بالمناسبة يا فانغ تاو
I was too harsh last time.
كنت قاس جدًا المرة الماضية
I'll toast you with juice.
سأحمّدك بالعصير
No worries. It was a misunderstanding.
لا قلقي، كان ذلك سوء تفاهم
I'm glad I didn't hurt you.
يسعدني أنني لم أؤذيك
It's ok.
إنه أوك
- Come on, Jiahuan. - I'll drink up.
- هيا يا جياهان - سأشرب لك
I'll drink to you, too.
سأشرب لك أيضًا
I'll join you.
أريد الانضمام إليك
Xiaoling, I think you'll have a boy.
شياو ولينغ، أعتقد أن لديك فتى
I think so, too.
أعتقد ذلك أيضا
Look, the girls in our family
انظري، الفتيات في عائلتنا
all had boys.
كان جميعهم من الفتيان
Mom gave birth to all the girls.
أنجبت أمي جميع الفتيات
It's time for us to have boys.
حان الوقت لنا أن يكون لدينا أولاد
Hey, you,
مرحبًا
do you have to rub it in?
هل عليك أن تفسد هذا؟
Xiaoling, I've got it.
شياو ولينغ، فهمت
What took you so long?
ما الذي أخّرك؟
Honey,
عزيزي
you wanted breakfast.
أردت الفطور
It's afternoon.
بعد الظهر
Where am I supposed to get it?
من أين يُفترض بي أن أحصل عليها؟
It shouldn't have taken you so long, though.
لكن لا يجب أن يستغرق الأمر وقتًا طويلًا
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
I've been looking all over the alley.
بحثت في كل مكان من الزقاق
Really. You wanted breakfast.
حقًا، أردت الفطور
Where can I get it in the afternoon?
من أين يمكنني الحصول عليها بعد الظهر؟
Chicken Soup Porridge?
حساء الدجاج؟
I couldn't get it.
لم أستطع الحصول عليها
I only got you fried pies.
أحضرت لك الحبوب المقلية فقط
I bought them all.
اشتريتها كلها
Give me.
أعطني
Eat while they are hot.
تناولي الطعام مع بعضهما
Eat.
كلي
Here.
تفضلي
It's ok for me to wait.
يصعب عليّ أن أنتظر
The point is,
المهم هو
can our baby wait?
هل يمكن لمرضينا أن ينتظر؟
Sure.
بالطبع
What's the smell?
ما هي رائحة؟
Did I stain myself with oil?
هل لطخت نفسي بالنفط؟
No, it's perfume.
لا إنه العطر
How can you smell perfume?
كيف يمكنك شم العطر؟
Where exactly have you been?
أين كنت بالضبط؟
I went to get you food.
ذهبت لأحضر لك الطعام
No wonder it took you three hours.
لا عجب أن الأمر استغرق ثلاث ساعات
Were you dancing in the park?
هل كنت ترقص في الحديقة؟
Absolutely not.
قطعًا لا
I went to get you food.
ذهبت لأحضر لك الطعام
The breakfast spot was closed.
أُغلق مكان الفطور
So I checked every place I could find.
لذلك راجعت كل مكان يمكنني العثور عليه
Tell me the truth.
أخبريني الحقيقة
I am telling the truth.
أنا أقول الحقيقة
I'm going to my mom's.
أنا ذاهبة إلى أمي
Be careful.
انتبه
Why are you going there?
لماذا تذهبين إلى هناك؟
To get some food.
للحصول على بعض الطعام
There's no food or drink. I'm starving.
لا يوجد الطعام أو المشروب، أنا أتضور جوعًا
Isn't this food?
أليس هذا الطعام؟
Liu Xiaoling.
ليو شياولينغ
Don't follow me.
لا تتبعني
Watch your belly.
انتبه لبطنك
- Get lost. - Well.
- اغرب عن وجهي - حسنا
Mom,
أمي
I'm staying at home tonight.
أنا أقيم في المنزل الليلة
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
He's gone too far.
تجاوز الحد
I put on so much weight
وضعت الكثير من الوزن
to give him a baby.
لإعطائه رضيعًا
I've been suffering every day,
كنت أعاني كل يوم
and he's out having fun.
ونستمتع بوقته
I wanted some Chicken Soup Porridge.
أردت بعضًا من حساء بورصة الدجاج
I asked him to get it.
طلبت منه الحصول عليه
But he kept me waiting for three hours.
لكنه أبقني أنتظر لمدة ثلاث ساعات
You were out for three hours.
كنت في الخارج لمدة ثلاث ساعات
What did you do?
ماذا فعلت؟
Did you go dancing again?
هل ذهبت ترقص مجددًا؟
- I'm starving. - Mom, let me explain.
- أنا أتضور جوعًا - أمي دعني أشرح لك
Chicken Soup Porridge, breakfast, right?
صوامع الدجاج، فطور، أليس كذلك؟
- Where could I get it? - Alright.
- من أين يمكنني الحصول عليها؟ - حسنًا
- I got several Fried Pies. - Enough.
- حصلت على العديد من لجان تقصي الحقائق الصديقة
Then she got mad at me.
ثم غضبة مني
Ok, get inside.
حسنا، ادخل
You're nothing like an adult.
لا شيء مثل شخص بالغ
Liu Xiaoling.
ليو شياولينغ
Alright, Zhenmin.
حسنا، جينمين
Go home.
اذهبي إلى المنزل
Let her stay here today.
دعها تبقى هنا اليوم
- No. - Go home.
- لا - اذهب إلى المنزل
Come and pick her up tomorrow.
تعالي وأحضرها غدًا
Ok, I'll do as you say.
حسنا، سأفعل ما تقول
I'll pick her up tomorrow.
سآخذها غدًا
Close the door.
اغلق الباب
Mom, talk to her.
أمي تحدثت معها
(Pickles)
(نقش)
Do you think we don't have enough trouble?
هل تظن أنه لا يوجد لدينا ما يكفي من المشاكل؟
Mom, I'm the victim.
أمي أنا الضحية
You should've beaten him up.
كان عليك أن تضربيه
You can stay here today.
يمكنك البقاء هنا اليوم
Go home with him tomorrow.
اذهب معه غدا
Every little thing happens,
كل شيء قليل يحدث
you dash back here.
عدت إلى هنا
You've got a family now.
لديك عائلة الآن
Don't be so impulsive.
لا تكن مندفعة
What's in it for you
ما خطبه لك
if you piss off your husband?
إذا كنت تشفق زوجك؟
Liu Xiaoling,
ليو شياولينغ
you bear my surname,
أنت تحمل لقبي
but why isn't your temper like mine?
لكن لماذا لا يشبه أعصابك مثلي؟
You can't cope with anything.
لا يمكنك تحمل أي شيء
Well, Mom,
حسنًا يا أمي
I'm carrying his baby
أنا أحمل طفلته
and he's doing this to me.
وهو يفعل هذا بي
After I give birth,
بعد أن أنجبت
who knows how he'll ignore me?
من يعرف كيف سيتجاهلي؟
Who is to blame?
من هو اللوم؟
Who insisted on marrying him?
من أصّر على الزواج منه؟
It's too late now.
فات الأوان الآن
You must follow your husband no matter what.
يجب أن تتبعي زوجك مهما كلف الأمر
I can get a divorce, then.
أستطيع الحصول على طلاق إذن
Liu Xiaoling, do whatever you want
ليو شياولينغ، افعل ما تريد
and act unreasonably.
وتتصرف بشكل غير معقول
You're going to suffer.
سوف تعاني
I'm just saying.
هذا رأيي فحسب
You can't say it.
لا يمكنك قول ذلك
You can't think about it.
لا يمكنك التفكير في الأمر
Not even a single thought.
ولا حتى فكرة واحدة
Now you are pregnant.
أنت الآن حامل
You must be responsible
يجب أن تكون مسؤولا
for everything you say,
عن كل ما تقوله
understand?
هل فهمت؟
Is it that serious?
هل الأمر بهذه الخطورة؟
Go home tomorrow.
اذهب إلى المنزل غدًا
Mom,
أمي
I want to eat Chicken Soup Porridge.
أريد أن آكل مطعم السوب للدجاج
I want it so much.
أريده كثيرًا
No Chicken Soup Porridge.
لا أحد مطعم دعونا نذهب
I'll make you Egg Drop Soup.
سأجعلك إيغ دروب
Zhenmin,
جينمين
apologize to Xiaoling.
اعتذري إلى شياو ولينغ
Honey,
عزيزي
I apologize to you.
أعتذر لك
Don't be mad.
لا تغضب
It's all my fault. I'm sorry.
هذا كله خطأي أنا آسف
Xiaoling, he apologized.
شياو ولينغ، اعتذر
Don't be angry.
لا تغضب
You have problems, too.
لديك مشاكل أيضًا
You're a hothead.
أنت غبية
She doesn't have any problem.
ليست لديها أي مشكلة
At this time,
في هذا الوقت
Zhenmin should take good care of her.
يجب أن يعتني بها جيدا
Zhenmin is careless
زنمين مهملة
and doesn't think things through.
ولا يفكروا في الأمور
But, Xiaoling,
ولكن شياو دينغ
I can assure you,
أستطيع أن أؤكد لك
he cares about you.
إنه يهتم بك
Do you think
هل تعتقد
this will work?
هل هذا سينجح؟
I asked Lixia
طلبت من ليكسيا
to take care of you
أن يعتني بك
until you give birth.
حتى الولادة
There will be no problem.
لن تكون هناك مشكلة
As for Zhenmin,
أما بالنسبة لزنمين
I will keep an eye on him.
سأراه
Are you happy?
هل أنت سعيد؟
You're lucky to have
أنت محظوظ لأنك تحظى
such a good sister-in-law.
وزوجة شقيقة جيدة
Exactly.
بالضبط
I'm flattered.
أشعر بالإطراء
Xiaoling may make
شياو مينغ قد تقدم
a great contribution to our family soon.
مساهمة كبيرة لعائلتنا قريبا
Have you checked?
هل راجعت؟
Not really.
ليس حقا
But a boy or a girl is equally good.
لكن الشاب أم الفتاة ماهر بنفس القدر
What about Youmin?
ماذا عن يومين؟
They haven't had a baby.
لم يتناولا طفلًا
Mom, Grandma,
أمي جدتي
I'll take good care of Xiaoling.
سأعتني جيدًا بشياو ولينغ
Honey,
عزيزي
concentrate on your pregnancy wellness.
ركز على سلامة حملك
Don't be mad at me.
لا تغضب مني
I promise I'll never
أعدك أنني لن أتمكن أبدًا
go dancing behind your back again.
اذهب لترقص خلف ظهرك مجددًا
Dad is also here. Dad,
أبي هنا أيضًا
I won't dance behind Xiaoling's back again.
لن أرقص خلف ظهر شياو مينغ مجددًا
Honey, don't be mad at me.
عزيزي، لا تغضب مني
- You promise? - I promise.
- قطعت وعدًا؟ - أضمن لك
Be good to me.
كن طيبًا معي
Of course.
بالطبع
(True Love for Life, Blessings)
(الحب الحقيقي من أجل الحياة، البركات)
(Blessings)
(البراءات)
Why can't I see anything?
لماذا لا يمكنني رؤية أي شيء؟
Is the contact lenses' prescription right?
هل وصفة العدسات الملاصقة؟
It's right.
إنه صحيح
They're genuine from Hendry Optical.
إنها حقيقية من نظرة الهندية
Can't you see? Did you wear it backwards?
ألا ترين؟ هل انتهيت منه إلى الخلف؟
Did you?
حقًا؟
- How about now? - Ok.
- ماذا عن الآن؟ - حسنا - حسنًا
Ok.
حسنا
You're all married.
أنت متزوجة جميعا
I'm getting old.
أنا أتقدم في السن
Jiali.
جيالي
They're coming.
إنه قادم
The groom!
العريس!
Come on.
هيا
The groom is here.
العريس هنا
He is coming.
إنه قادم
Fang Tao.
فانغ تاو
- Red packets first! - Red packets.
- الحزم الحمراء أولًا! - الحزم الحمراء - حزم أحمر
Sure, I've got them prepared.
بالطبع، لقد جعلتها جاهزة
You each have one.
كل واحد منكم لديه واحد
Two.
اثنان
Give me, Fang Tao.
أعطني، فانغ تاو
I'll hand them out for you.
سأرسلهم لك
Come in, please.
ادخل، من فضلك
Come on in.
تفضلي بالدخول
- Grandma, Mom. - He's here.
- جددا يا أمي - إنه هنا
Get in.
اركبي
She's waiting for you.
إنها بانتظارك
Jiali.
جيالي
You look sharp.
تبدين واضحة
Jiahuan,
جياهان
let's go home.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل
Slow down.
تمهلي
Come on.
هيا
The first car.
السيارة الأولى
Feng.
فنغ
Watch out.
احترس
- Feng, come here. - Get in the car.
- فنغ، تعالي إلى هنا - اركب السيارة
Sit tight.
اجلس جيدًا
Which car do I get in?
أي سيارة دخلت؟
Be patient.
اصطبر
There's a lot to do. You stay with me.
هناك الكثير مما يجب فعله، أنت تبقى معي
- Come. - Jiawen, you guys go first.
- هيا - جيان وين، اذهبوا أولا
Ok.
حسنا
We'll be there soon.
سنصل إلى هناك قريبا
Go ahead.
تفضل
You didn't cry at Xiaoling's wedding.
لم تبكي في حفل زفاف شياولينغ
What's wrong with you today?
ما خطبك اليوم؟
They got married one by one.
تزوجوا واحدًا بعد الآخر
Only the youngest is left with me.
لم يتبق معي سوى الأصغر سنًا
That's the way it should be.
هذه هي الطريقة التي ينبغي أن يكون عليها
Phone.
هاتف
Hello.
مرحبًا
Mom, is Jiali home with you?
أمي، هل عاد جيالي معك؟
Xiaoling is in labor.
شياو ولينغ في سوق العمل
Come to the hospital.
تعالي إلى المستشفى
She did it on purpose.
فعلت ذلك عن قصد
She always tries to get ahead of me.
إنها تحاول دائمًا أن تسبقني
She fought with me, like always.
قاتلت معي، كالعادة
She did it on purpose.
فعلت ذلك عمدًا
Today is my big day.
اليوم هو يومي الكبير
I told her not to come,
طلبت منها ألا تأتي
but she had to.
لكن كان عليها ذلك
Now what? She's got us in a big mess.
الآن ماذا؟ تسببت بنا في فوضى كبيرة
All our guests
كل ضيوفنا
went to watch her give birth.
ذهب لمشاهدتها وهي تلد
Not many people went.
لم يذهب الكثير من الناس
Wasn't our wedding lively?
ألم يكن حفل زفافنا حيويا؟
Not at all!
لا على الإطلاق
Without the leading role,
بدون الدور الرئيسي
what's the point of supporting roles?
ما الفائدة من الأدوار المساندة؟
You're the leading role.
أنت الدور الرئيسي
If it upsets you so much,
إذا كان ذلك يزعجك كثيرًا
we can have one too.
يمكننا الحصول على واحد أيضا
Get out.
اخرجي
It's not that easy to have a baby.
ليس من السهل الحصول على طفل
It can be hard
يمكن أن يكون الأمر صعبا
and easy.
سهلا
If it's so easy,
إذا كان الأمر سهلا جدا
why haven't you had one
لماذا لم يكن لديك واحد
over so many years?
على مدى سنوات عديدة؟
It was my ex-wife's problem.
كانت مشكلة زوجتي السابقة
Who knows if you're lying?
من يعلم إن كنت تكذب؟
Then I can only
إذن لا يمكنني إلا
prove it with my strength.
أن أثبت ذلك بقوتي
I haven't taken off my contact lenses!
لم أخلع عدسات الاتصال الخاصة بي!
He's asleep.
إنه نائم
What's the point?
ما الفائدة؟
Getting married, having kids, raising kids,
الزواج، وإنجاب الأطفال، وتربية الأطفال
getting old, and dying.
و- التقدم في السن والوفاة
That's the whole point of being a woman.
هذه كل شيء لأنها امرأة
It's so much easier to be a man.
من الأسهل بكثير أن يكون رجلا
They don't give birth or feed babies.
لا يلبون أو يطعمون أطفالا
They don't care about anything.
إنهم لا يهتمون أي شيء
I'm sure Zhenmin is dancing now.
أنا متأكد من أن جينمين رقص الآن
l don't think he is that kind of man.
لا يعتقد أنه ذلك النوع من الرجال
He cares about you.
إنه يهتم بك
Are you kidding?
هل تمزح؟
I asked him to name our son,
طلبت منه أن يسمي ابنا
but he hasn't done it yet.
لكنه لم يفعل ذلك بعد
Jiayi, I've realized now
جيايي، لقد أدركت الآن
that getting married was a mistake.
أن الزواج كان خطأ
Why don't you
لماذا لا تعطيه اسمًا
give him a name?
إعطائه اسمًا؟
I?
أنا؟
I'm not very educated.
أنا لست متعلمةً جدًا
As long as it sounds good.
طالما أنه يبدو جيدًا
Jiayi,
جيايي
bring me the music score.
أحضري لي درجة الموسيقى
Music score? Which one?
درجة موسيقى؟ أي واحدة؟
The one on the left.
والذي على اليسار
Will it work?
هل سينجح
I'll call him whatever I read.
سأتصل به مهما قرأت
This one is good.
هذا جيد
The sun is shining.
الشمس تألق
Yangyang, referring to shining.
يانغيانغ، تشير إلى التألق
Ok.
حسنا
Tang Yangyang.
تانغ يانغانغ
Good name.
اسم جيد
Xiaoling, I'm home.
شياو ولينغ، عدت إلى المنزل
You're here, Jiayi.
أنت هنا يا جيايي
Your wife needs you to take care of her.
يجب على زوجتك أن تعتني بها
Don't run around.
لا تركضي
Stay with her.
ابقي معها
Did you hear her?
هل سمعتها؟
Yes, I know. You're wrong about me.
نعم أعرف أنت مخطئ فيّ
I went to get Xiaoling good food.
ذهبت للحصول على طعام لذيذ شياولينغ
What did you buy? Let me see.
ماذا اشتريت؟ دعني أرى
Fried Glutinous Rice Bar and Dough Twist.
وداي تويست
Luckily I was quick.
لحسن الحظ كنت سريعًا
This is all that's left.
هذا هو كل ما تبقى
Xiaoling, take a rest.
شياو ولينغ، خذ قسطا من الراحة
I have to go.
يجب أن أذهب
Zhenmin,
تشينمين
take care of Xiaoling.
اعتني بشياولينغ
Rest assured, Jiayi.
كن مطمئنا يا جيايي
I'm leaving.
سأغادر
Tie this up.
اربّثي هذا
Ok.
حسنا
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعلين؟
What do you think?
ما رأيك
Whose car is this? It's kind of sharp.
سيارة من هذه؟ إنها حادة نوعًا ما
It's ours, of course.
إنها الخاصة بنا بالطبع
- Come. - Really?
- تعال - هيا - حقًا؟
Get in the car.
اركب السيارة
Do we have a car?
هل لدينا سيارة؟
Let's go home.
لنذهب إلى المنزل
How do you like it?
كيف يعجبك؟
Honey, how much is it?
عزيزي، كم ثمن؟
180,000 yuan.
180يوان
So expensive!
باهظة الثمن!
(May Day Shopping Mall)
"حمام المشاجرة في مايو"
Give them to your mom.
أعطهم لأمك
I don't wear fancy clothes.
أنا لا أرتدي ملابس فاخرة
Grandma, elderly people
جدتي، المسنين
should wear something colorful.
يجب أن يرتدي شيئًا باردًا
This is yours.
هذه ملكك
No, no.
لا
- I'll look like a weirdo in it. - It's nice!
- سأبدو غريبة فيه - - إنه لطيف! - نعم!
Summer purchase of winter apparel.
شراء ملابس شتوية في الصيف
It's a gift from your granddaughter.
إنها هدية من جدتك
Keep it.
احتفظي بها
Mom, this is yours.
أمي هذه لك
Leather jacket?
سترةً جلدية؟
Yes.
نعم
The leather is good.
الجلود جيدة
And the price is high.
والأسعار مرتفعة
How much?
كم؟
200?
200؟
One more zero.
صفرا آخر
2000?
عام 2000؟
- Return it. - Why?
- أعيديه - لماذا؟
- I don't want it. - Too expensive.
- لا أريده - باهظ الثمن جدًا
I paid for it with my money, not yours.
دفعت ثمنها بأموالي وليس بأموالك
Still, I don't want to cost you so much.
مع ذلك، لا أريد أن أكلفك كثيرًا
You've worked hard all your life.
عملت بجد طوال حياتك
Why don't you reward yourself?
لم لا تكافئين نفسك؟
It's nice. Look!
إنه جميل، انظري!
Return it. Do you have the receipt?
أعيده، هل لديك الإيصال؟
Why do you have to return it?
لماذا عليك أن تعيده؟
There are more.
هناك المزيد
Jiayi,
جيايي
don't be extravagant
لا تكن مبتسرا
when you are rich.
عندما تكون غنيا
Always prepare for the worst.
دائما للاستعداد للأسوأ
Grandma,
جدتي
how many good days can you have in life?
كم يوم جيد في الحياة؟
If you don't please yourself on good days,
إن لم أرجوك في الأيام الجيدة
it will be too late for regrets on bad days.
سيتأخر الوقت على الندم في الأيام السيئة
Put on a show when you're given a stage.
ضعي معروفًا عندما يتم إعطاؤك مشهدًا
Life is art.
الحياة فن
Art is life.
المادة هي الحياة
Good!
جيد!
They are all yours.
إنها لك كلها
All of these.
كل هذه
Let me grab a bite. I'm starving.
دعني أحضر قضمة، أنا أتضور جوعًا
Where did you learn that? Look at her.
أين تعلمت ذلك؟ انظروا إليها
No one listens to us anymore.
لم يعد أحد يصغي إلينا
We're getting old.
نحن نتقدم في السن
How can you say that in front of me?
كيف يمكنك قول ذلك أمامي؟
I am the old one.
أنا القديم
Those who shouldn't be dead were gone,
أولئك الذين لا ينبغي أن يكونوا قد ذهبوا
leaving only us behind,
وبتركنا فقط
the ones who should be dead.
أولئك الذين يجب أن يكونوا ميوتين
Look, here you go again.
انظري، ها أنت ذي مجددًا
Why don't you say something nice?
لماذا لا تقول شيئًا لطيفًا؟
You're alive for a good reason.
أنت على قيد الحياة لسبب وجيه
When will Jiahuan give birth?
متى سيولد جياهان؟
In two or three months, probably.
في غضون شهرين أو ثلاثة، على الأرجح
You know what,
هل تعرف
last night I dreamed
حلمت ليلة أمس
that she had a son.
أنها حصلت على ابن
Really?
حقًا؟
Another son?
ابن آخر؟
From your mouth to God's ear.
من فمك إلى أذن الله
(Two months later)
بعد شهرين
(Huainan AH Trust Investment Corporation)
(Huaanan Aه Trust Investment Corporation)
(Time is money.) Be careful.
(الوقت وقت المال) توخي الحذر
(Efficiency is life.)
(الكفاءة هي الحياة)
What would you like to eat today?
ماذا تريدين أن تأكلي اليوم؟
Something light.
بعض الضوء
You're tired of my cooking.
سئمت من طبخي
We've been to every restaurant in town.
ذهبنا إلى كل مطعم في المدينة
I don't know what you would like.
لا أعرف ماذا تريد
- Slowly. - That's why
- ببطء - هذا هو السبب
I got so heavy.
أصبح ثقيلًا جدًا
All women gain weight during pregnancy.
يزداد وزن كل النساء أثناء الحمل
You're much better than others.
أنت أفضل بكثير من الآخرين
Putting on weight hasn't affected your face.
لم يؤثر الوزن على وجهك
You'll be back in shape after giving birth.
ستعود إلى الوضع بعد الولادة
That's why it's hard for women.
لهذا السبب الأمر صعب على النساء
Jiahuan,
جياهووان
I know it's hard for you.
أعلم أن هذا صعب عليك
You only have to give birth to the baby.
عليك فقط أن تلد الطفل
I'll take care of it.
سأهتم بالأمر
Hang in there.
اصمد
You don't know
أنت لا تعرف
that some people are trying
أن بعض الناس يحاولون
to take over my job
لتولي عملي
while I'm pregnant.
بينما أنا حامل
I don't think you'll give it to them.
لا أظن أنك ستأعطيهن إياه
Even if I give it to them,
حتى لو أعطيهم إياه
are they capable of doing it?
هل هم قادرون على القيام بذلك؟
The same job
نفس العمل
done by different people
يقوم بها أشخاص مختلفون
can lead to different results.
يمكن أن يؤدي إلى نتائج مختلفة
Yes.
نعم
But don't work so hard.
لكن لا تجهد نفسك بالعمل
The company can function without anyone.
يمكن للشركة أن تعمل من دون أحد
Slow down.
تمهلي
You got the point.
لقد فهمت الهدف
It can't function
لا يمكن أن يعمل
without me.
من دوني
So
لذلك
I can't let them
لا أستطيع السماح لهم
take advantage
الاستفادة
of my pregnancy.
من حملتي
Sure.
بالطبع
I absolutely support your decision.
أؤيد قرارك تمامًا
So I take you to and from work every day.
لذلك آخذك إلى العمل ومنها كل يوم
Today at the meeting,
اليوم في الاجتماع
Wu pulled a long face.
سحب وو وجها طويلا
I'm going to prove to them
لن أثبت لهم
that a woman
أن المرأة
can take care of both work and family
يمكن أن تهتم بالعمل والأسرة
and can do it well.
ويمكنه القيام بذلك جيدا
Well, well, well.
حسنًا
You're the Iron Lady of our family.
أنت السيدة الحديدي لعائلتنا
Alright, let's stop talking about work.
حسنًا لنتوقف عن الحديث عن العمل
Think about what you'd like to eat.
فكري فيما تريد أن تأكليه
Don't ask me everything, everyday.
لا تسألني عن كل شيء، يوميًا
You're in charge of our family.
أنت المسؤولة عن عائلتنا
Who else can I ask but you?
من يمكنني أن أسأل لكنك غيرك؟
Be careful.
توخي الحذر
Light.
خفيفة
What light food can I get you?
ما هو الطعام الخفيف الذي يمكنني الحصول عليه لك؟
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
ما الخطب؟ هل تأذيت؟
Where are you hurt?
أين أُصبت؟
- Belly. - Belly...
- بلي - بلي...
Hospital.
المستشفى
You're like your sisters.
أنت مثل أختاتك
None of you gave us any warning.
لم يمنحنا أي منكم أي تحذير
Jiahuan, hang in there.
مرحبًا، اصمد
Hang in there.
تماسك
(Huainan AH Trust Investment Corporation)
(هوايان آه الاستئماني للاستثمار)
(Huainan No.1 People's Hospital, Outpatient)
(مستشفى هوان رقم 1 الشعبي، المرضى الخارجيين)
Look.
انظر
He looks just like you when you were little.
إنه يشبهك تمامًا في صغرك
Thick eyebrows and big eyes.
حاجبان كثيفان وعينان كبيرتان
Mom,
أمي
who says that about a little girl?
من قال ذلك عن فتاة صغيرة؟
You looked like a boy when you were little.
كنت تشبه الصبي في صغرك
Where's Grandma?
أين جدتي؟
Her legs were weak,
ساقيها كانا ضعيفين
so I didn't let her come.
لذلك لم أسمح لها بالمجيء
Jiawen isn't well.
جياوين ليست بخير
Xiaoling has to take care of the baby.
شياو مينغ يجب أن تعتني بالطفل
Jiaxi is at work.
جياشي في العمل
After your recovery period
بعد فترة تعافيك
and the baby's first month,
وشهر الطفل الأول
we'll celebrate together.
سنحتفل معا
Jianguo and I will
أنا وجيانغو
organize a banquet for you.
تنظيم مأدبه لك
Our family is getting bigger
عائلتنا تزداد أكبر
and busier.
وأكثر انشغالا
Leave these things to us.
اتركي هذه الأشياء لنا
We'll pay for Jiahuan's
سندفع ثمن مأدبة جياهان
celebration banquet.
مأدبة الاحتفال
Nobody's competing with me.
لم يتنافس أحد معي
Jinman Restaurant.
مطعم جينمان
Thanks, Jiayi, Ouyang.
شكرًا يا جيايي أويانغ
After your recovery period,
بعد فترة تعافيك
you should cook once in a while.
يجب أن تطبخ مرة واحدة بين الحين والآخر
You're a mom now.
أنت أم الآن
Don't let Fang do all the housework.
لا تدع فانغ يقوم بكل العمل المنزلي
Jiali, cooking is no big deal.
جيالي، الطهي ليس بالأمر الجلل
I'm just worried
أنا قلق فقط
about Jiahuan's recovery.
على شفاء جياهان
I don't have parents
ليس لدي آباء
or female relatives.
أو اﻷقارب من اﻹناث
I know nothing about postnatal recovery.
لا شيء فيما يتعلق بالشفاء بعد الولادة
Jiahuan, I'd like to help you,
جياهوان، أود أن أساعدك
but I can't do much.
لكن لا يمكنني فعل الكثير
I'm a light sleeper at night.
أنا أشعر بالنعاس في الليل
Aren't you busy selling pickles?
ألست مشغول ببيع المخللات؟
My daughter and grandson are more important.
ابنتي وحفيدي أكثر أهمية
It's ok, Jiahuan.
قولك يا جياهان
After I gave birth,
بعد أن أنجبت
there was no one around.
لا يوجد أحد هنا
Ouyang was the only one
كانت أويانغ هي الوحيدة
taking care of me. You'll be fine.
يعتني بي ستكون بخير
If there's no other way,
إذا لم تكن هناك طريقة أخرى
I'll ask Qiufang
سأطلب تشي وفانغ
to see if she can
لمعرفة ما إذا كانت تستطيع
find someone in Dahebo.
العثور على شخص في داهيبو
Why do you ask for trouble?
لماذا تطلبين المشاكل؟
You can borrow Ms. Liao for a month.
يمكنك استعارة السيدة لياو لمدة شهر
Jiayi,
جياي
can you manage without her?
هل يمكنك تدبر أمرها من دونها؟
Of course.
بالطبع
I'll pay her salary.
سأدفع راتبها
Have you named him?
هل سميته؟
Yes, before he was born.
نعم، قبل أن يولد
What is it?
ما الأمر؟
Zhicheng.
جيتشنغ
It means where there's a will, there's a way.
إنه يعني أين توجد إرادة هناك طريقة
- Be careful. - Ok.
- كوني حذرة - توخي الحذر - حسنا
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك
- I'll go up first. It's slippery. - Ok.
- سأصعد أولًا، إنها زميلة - حسنًا
Come.
هيا
- Slowly. - Ok.
- ببطء - حسنا
Oh, my.
يا إلهي
It's here.
إنه هنا
Let's sit here.
لنجلس هنا
- Here. - Ok.
- هيا - حسنا
Well, what are we looking at?
إلام ننظر؟
There's no sign of the moon.
لا توجد علامة على القمر
Be patient.
كوني مريضا
The forecast calls
النداءات المتوقعة
for cloudy turning to clear tonight.
للتحول الغيوم إلى إزالة الليلة
Alright.
حسنا
I miss you.
أشتاق إليك
Seriously?
حقًا؟
It wasn't long after we met.
لم يمض وقت طويل على التقينا
But I feel like it's been a long time.
لكنني أشعر أن الوقت قد حان
You wouldn't let me go to your house.
لم تدعني أذهب إلى منزلك
I've waited from day to night.
لقد انتظرت من ليلة إلى أخرى
I didn't make you wait.
لم أجعلك تنتظر
Jiaxi.
جياشي
May I kiss you?
هل يمكنني أن قبّلك؟
The moon's coming out.
القمر يخرج
Look, hurry up. Make a wish.
اسرعي، تمني أمنية
Ok.
حسنا
Thank you, moon.
شكرا لك يا القمر
Hongyu, do you know what I wished for?
هونغيو، هل تعرف ما تمنيت له؟
Hongyu.
هونغيو
Hongyu?
هونغيو؟
Don't scare me.
لا تخفني
Yan Hongyu!
يان هونغوي!
Wang.
وانغ
- Hello. - What happened?
- مرحبًا - ماذا حدث؟
Did Jiaxi hit him?
هل ضربه جياشي؟
Come with me.
تعال معي
She didn't.
لم تفعل
When they were dating,
عندما كانا يتواعدان
he fell.
سقط
Fell?
سقطت؟
Where is Jiaxi?
أين جياشي؟
She went to work.
ذهبت إلى العمل
Then why did you ask me to come?
إذن لماذا طلبت مني المجيء
You've seen
رأيت
what's happening here.
ماذا يحدث هنا
What's happening here?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
The kids.
الأطفال
What about them?
ماذا عنهم؟
A good thing is happening.
يحدث شيء جيد
Can't you tell?
ألا يمكنك أن تخبرني؟
Hongyu and Jiaxi.
هونغ يو وجياشي
A seed is dropped
يتم إسقاط البذور
and a sprout grows.
ونمو الزهور
They've fallen in love.
لقد وقعت في الحب
Wang,
وانغ
I asked Jiaxi to be your apprentice,
طلبت من جياشي أن تكون تلميذك
not your daughter-in-law.
وليس زوجة ابنك
Jiali, I'll tell you what,
جيو الي، سأخبرك أمرًا
you shouldn't blame me for this.
لا يجب أن تلومني على هذا
I tried to stop them,
حاولت إيقافهم
but they are in free love.
لكنهم في الحب الحر
There's nothing I could do.
لا شيء يمكنني فعله
No, definitely not.
لا، بالتأكيد لا
Don't be so authoritarian,
لا تكن استبداديا جدًا
I'm telling you.
أنا أقول لك
We must not
يجب ألا
break them up.
انفصالهم
Ok.
حسنا
Thanks.
شكرا
Here's your change.
إليك التغيير
Ok.
حسنا
Mom, you knew about this already.
أمي لقد علمت بهذا بالفعل
Why didn't you tell me?
لماذا لم تخبريني
I forgot.
نسيت
There's so much going on in the family.
هناك الكثير الذي يجري في الأسرة
I have to worry about Xiaoling,
يجب أن أقلق بشأن شياو ولينغ
Jiahuan,
جياوان
and Jiawen.
وجيوين
I've got a lot on my mind.
تشغل بالي أمور كثيرة
Besides, Jiaxi is still young.
إلى جانب ذلك، جياشي لا يزال صغيرا
It's not going that fast.
لن يحدث ذلك بسرعة
I warned her.
حذرتها
Not that fast?
ليست بهذه السرعة؟
You know what,
هل تعرف
they're on their last leg.
إنهما على ساقهما الأخير
Wang Huaimin is a mean woman.
وانغ هوايمين امرأة شريرة
How can you marry Jiaxi to her son?
كيف يمكنك أن تتزوج جياشي من ابنها؟
She's like a hornet's nest.
إنها مثل عش الحصان
You'll get stung if you get close to her.
سوف تستطيعين إذا اقتربت منها
We're even in-laws with the Tangs.
نحن أصهار حتى مع الأواني
Why are we afraid of her?
لماذا نخاف منها؟
Don't oppose it so fiercely this time.
لا تعارض الأمر بشراسة هذه المرة
Like the last two times,
كالمرتين الأخيرتين
the more you opposed it,
كلما عارضت ذلك
the more you pushed them together.
كلما دفعتهما معا أكثر
Did Jiaxi tell you anything?
هل أخبرك جياشي بأي شيء؟
No.
لا
No one told me anything.
لم يخبرني أحد بأي شيء
Didn't you just tell me that?
ألم تخبريني بذلك فحسب
Let's talk about it at home, ok?
لنتحدث عن الأمر في المنزل، صحيح؟
I've got business to do.
لديّ ما أقوم به
In the final analysis,
في التحليل النهائي
it's your and Jianguo's fault.
إنه خطأ أنت وجيانغو
Why don't you care about her?
لماذا لا تهتم بها؟
It's time to date once she has a job.
حان الوقت لأوامرها
You know many young officers.
أنت تعرف الكثير من الضباط الشباب
Set her up with them.
ضبطها معهم
Mom, I set her up with them.
أمي لقد ضبطتها معهم
But she wouldn't see them.
لكنها لن تراها
An elder sister is like a mom.
الأخت الكبرى مثل والدة
But you're her mom!
لكنك والدتها!
Go home.
اذهبي إلى المنزل
You've pissed off the God of Wealth.
لقد قضيت إله الثروة
Hello, Mrs. He.
مرحبًا يا سيدة هي
You're...
أنت...
I'm Jiali's colleague
أنا زميلة جيالي
from the Commerce Bureau.
من مكتب التجارة
Jiali's colleague?
زميل جيالي؟
Sit down, please.
اجلسي من فضلك
I've known Meixin
لقد عرفت مكسين
for a long time.
لفترة طويلة
We came to Huainan together.
جئنا إلى هوينان معا
Mrs. He, it's me.
السيدة هي، هذا أنا
Don't you recognize me?
ألا تعرفني؟
I tend to be a bit forgetful.
عادة ما أنسى بعض الشيء
I don't recall.
لا أتذكر
Xinhuai Village, Wang Huaimin.
قرية شينوواي، وانغ هوامين
I kind of remember.
أتذكر بعض الشيء
Remember, huh?
تذكر، هوه؟
Are you here to see Jiali
هل أنت هنا لرؤية جيالي
or Meixin?
أو ميشين؟
I came to see you.
جئت لرؤيتك
I'm here for something big,
أنا هنا من أجل شيء كبير
something happy.
شيء سعيد
Something happy?
شيء سعيد؟
Mrs. He, congratulations.
السيدة هي، تهانيّ
Why?
لماذا؟
As an old woman,
كامرأة كبيرة
what happy thing can I have?
ما هو الشيء السعيد الذي يمكنني الحصول عليه؟
Look,
انظر
your youngest granddaughter,
حبيبتك الصغرى
Jiaxi, has a happy thing.
جياشي، لديها شيء سعيد
It's just like you have a happy thing.
كل ما في الأمر أن لديك شيئا سعيدا
Jiaxi and
جياشي
Hongyu, my son,
هونغ يو، ابني
fell for each other at first sight.
وقع كل منهما على الآخر من النظرة الأولى
They're in free love.
إنه في الحب الحر
They're just fooling around.
إنهما مجرد خداع
Don't take it seriously.
لا تأخذها على محمل الجد
No.
لا
They are taking it seriously,
إنهم يأخذونها على محمل الجد
not fooling around.
وليس المزاح
I'm here
أنا هنا
to propose to Jiaxi.
لاقتراح على جياشي
As Hongyu's mom,
كما هي والدة هونغ يو
I heartily agree.
وأنا أتفق مع ذلك في ذلك
If that's the case,
إذا كان هذا هو الحال
you're not the only one
أنت لست الوحيد
who has to agree to it,
من عليه أن يوافق عليه
right?
صحيح
Yeah, of course.
نعم بالطبع
It only works out if both families
انها تنجح فقط إذا كانت كلتا العائلتين سعيدتين بها
are happy with it, right?
سعيدة بذلك، أليس كذلك؟
I see.
فهمت
When they get back,
عندما يعودون
I'll tell them.
سأخبرهم
We will
سوف
discuss it and have a meeting.
نناقشه ونعقد اجتماعًا
Have a meeting?
هل هناك اجتماع؟
It's like an underground organization.
إنها مثل منظمة سرية
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Mrs. He, look.
يا سيدة هو، انظري
It's my first time to visit you
إنها المرة الأولى لي لزيارتك
and I don't know what to buy.
ولا أعرف ماذا يمكنني الشراء
This is a small token of my regard.
هذا رمز صغير عن احترامي
Please take it.
يرجى أخذها
I can't take the money.
لا يمكنني أخذ المال
I'm not in charge of the family.
أنا لست مسؤولا عن الأسرة
Take it.
خذه
- No. - Do take it.
- لا - خذ الأمر
If you keep this up,
إن احتفظت بهذا
I won't let you in again.
لن أسمح لك بالدخول مجددًا
Well...
إذن
Bye.
إلى اللقاء
Get me some pickles.
اجلب لي بعض المخللات
Wang!
وانغ!
Eight Pickled Vegetables, huh?
ثمانية خيوط مخللة، هوه؟
- This. - Ok.
- هذا - حسنا
Ok.
حسنا
- Anything else? - Pepper.
- أي شيء آخر؟ - الفلفل
Ok. Ok.
حسنا
Come on.
هيا
Done.
تماما
Ok.
حسنا
Here you are. Free of charge.
ها أنت ذا، مجانية
Meixin, don't do this.
ميشين، لا تفعلي هذا
It's a horse of another color.
إنه حصان من لون آخر
If you do this...
إن قمت بهذا...
No, if you do this, I won't come again.
لا، إن فعلت هذا، لن آتي مجددًا
- Take it. - Ok.
- خذها - حسنا
I'll take your money.
سآخذ أموالك
Thanks.
شكرًا
Meixin.
مكسين
Do you remember,
هل تتذكرين
when we came to Huainan together,
عندما أتينا إلى هوينان معًا
Hu, the blind guy, told us our fortunes.
هو الشاب الأعمى أخبرنا بثرواتنا
Hu said we were sisters
قال هو إننا أختان
in our last life,
في حياتنا الأخيرة
and we could become relatives in this life.
ويمكن أن نصبح أقرباء في هذه الحياة
The blind guy, the fortune teller?
الرجل الأعمى، عرافة الحظ؟
You can't believe what he said.
لا أصدّق ما قاله
I'm telling you,
أنا أقول لك
it's true.
هذا صحيح
You have to believe it.
عليك أن تصدق ذلك
We will
سوف نصبح أقرباء
become relatives.
إلى أقرباء؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني؟
Don't you know?
ألا تعرفين؟
Hongyu, my son,
هونغ يو، ابني
is dating Jiaxi, your daughter.
يساعد جياشي، ابنتك
I'm telling you,
أنا أقول لك
as their moms, we must be supportive.
والدتهم، يجب أن نكون داعمين
You must take the money.
يجب أن تأخذ المال
Consider it a deposit.
اعتبره وديعة
- No. - It's a deposit.
- لا - إنه إيداع
You know what,
هل تعرف
it's settled.
حسنا، لقد سويت
No, no.
لا
- It's settled. - It's not right.
- لقد تمت تسويتها - هذا ليس صحيحًا
- Settled. It's settled. - Wang!
- تم تسوية، لقد استقرت - وانغ!
- Don't change your mind.
- لا تغير رأيك
- Wang. - Settled.
- وانغ - تم استرداده
♪Thoughts linger with snowflakes flying♪
♪ دموع مدهشة برككات ثلجية تطير ♪
♪Warm memories never fade away♪
♪ ذكريات الصحراء لا تتلاشى أبدا ♪
♪Those past stories and moments♪
♪ تلك القصص واللحظات الماضية ♪
♪Find their peace in silent years♪
♪ ابحث عن السلام في سنوات صامتة ♪
♪The memories buried deep inside♪
♪ الذكريات مدفونة في العمق ♪
♪Gains or losses, hope you're fine♪
♪ مكاسب أو خسائر، آمل أن تكون بخير ♪
♪Time takes people away♪
♪ الوقت يبعد الناس ♪
♪Leaving their loved ones behind♪
♪ التخلي عن أحبائهم ♪
♪What can I offer you♪
♪ ما الذي يمكنني أن أقدم لك ♪
♪Mountains, rivers, and clouds♪
♪ الجبال والأنهار والسحب ♪
♪What can I give back to you♪
♪ ما الذي يمكنني إعادته إليك ♪
♪My heart is restless♪
♪ قلبي قلق ♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
♪ ما الذي يمكنني أن أترك لك ♪
♪There are no fireworks in the city♪
♪ لا توجد الألعاب النارية في المدينة ♪
♪How can I tell you♪
♪ كيف يمكنني أن أقول لك ♪
♪Flowers bloom in distant corners♪
♪ الزهور تزهر في أركان بعيدة ♪
♪What can I leave to you♪
♪ ماذا يمكن أن أترك لك ♪
♪There are no fireworks in the city♪
♪ لا توجد الألعاب النارية في المدينة ♪
♪How can I tell you♪
♪ كيف يمكنني أن أقول لك ♪
♪Flowers bloom in distant corners♪
♪ الزهور تزهر في أركان بعيدة ♪